export const quizQuestions = [
  {
    question:
      "Which programming language was created by Dennis Ritchie in 1972?",
    options: ["COBOL", "C", "Python", "Smurf Language"],
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the first electronic computer, built in 1946?",
    options: ["ENIAC", "EDVAC", "UNIVAC", "Terminator"],
    answer: "ENIAC",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the Google search algorithm?",
    options: ["PageRank", "GoogleBot", "Bing", "Brain Juice"],
    answer: "PageRank",
  },
  {
    question: "Which programming language was created by Yukihiro Matsumoto?",
    options: ["Ruby", "JavaScript", "Python", "Java"],
    answer: "Ruby",
  },
  {
    question: "Which operating system was developed by Linus Torvalds?",
    options: ["Windows", "macOS", "Android", "Linux"],
    answer: "Linux",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the protocol used to transfer files on the web?",
    options: ["HTTP", "FTP", "SMTP", "Pizza Transfer Protocol"],
    answer: "FTP",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the main use of the SQL programming language?",
    options: [
      "Database Management",
      "Web Development",
      "Scientific Computing",
      "Writing Novels",
    ],
    answer: "Database Management",
  },
  {
    question: "Which company developed the Java programming language?",
    options: ["Microsoft", "Apple", "Sun Microsystems", "Pieds Nickel√©s Inc."],
    answer: "Sun Microsystems",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the main difference between IPv4 and IPv6?",
    options: [
      "IP Address Size",
      "Connection Speed",
      "Security",
      "Pizza Flavor",
    ],
    answer: "IP Address Size",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the IBM supercomputer that played 'Jeopardy!'?",
    options: ["Deep Blue", "Watson", "AlphaGo", "Super Skynet"],
    answer: "Watson",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the main use of the R programming language?",
    options: [
      "Web Development",
      "Scientific Computing",
      "Artificial Intelligence",
      "Creating Memes",
    ],
    answer: "Scientific Computing",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the markup language used to structure web page content?",
    options: ["HTML", "CSS", "JavaScript", "Chocolate Cake"],
    answer: "HTML",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the unit of measurement for hard disk storage capacity?",
    options: ["Byte", "Bit", "Nibble", "Croissant"],
    answer: "Byte",
  },
  {
    question: "Which technology is used to create 3D images in web browsers?",
    options: ["WebGL", "HTML5", "CSS3", "Oil Painting"],
    answer: "WebGL",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the inventor of the typewriter?",
    options: [
      "Christopher Latham Sholes",
      "Charles Babbage",
      "Herman Hollerith",
      "Mad Hatter",
    ],
    answer: "Christopher Latham Sholes",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the speed of light in fiber optics?",
    options: ["300,000 km/s", "225,000 km/s", "200,000 km/s", "1 snail/s"],
    answer: "225,000 km/s",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the lossless image format?",
    options: ["JPEG", "GIF", "PNG", "Dinosaur Format"],
    answer: "PNG",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the famous artificial intelligence test proposed by Alan Turing?",
    options: [
      "Turing Test",
      "Farnsworth Test",
      "Voight-Kampff Test",
      "Pea Test",
    ],
    answer: "Turing Test",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the neural network developed by Google for image recognition?",
    options: ["Inception", "ResNet", "VGG", "PicassoNet"],
    answer: "Inception",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the founder of SpaceX?",
    options: ["Jeff Bezos", "Richard Branson", "Elon Musk", "Buzz Lightyear"],
    answer: "Elon Musk",
  },
];
